<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 class=&#34;heading heading--1&#34; id=&#34;code-of-conduct&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;heading heading--2&#34; id=&#34;purpose&#34;&gt;Purpose&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A primary goal of all the conferences and user groups that refer to this Code of Conduct is to be inclusive to the largest number of contributors, with the most varied and diverse backgrounds possible. As such, we are committed to providing a friendly, safe and welcoming environment for all, regardless of gender, sexual orientation, ability, ethnicity, socioeconomic status and religion (or lack thereof).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Code of Conduct outlines our expectations for all those who participate in our community, as well as the consequences for unacceptable behavior.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haoting Shen</title>
      <link>/speakers/haoting-shen-726b25f8-a400-4d8e-aa9f-6873e86f958b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/speakers/haoting-shen-726b25f8-a400-4d8e-aa9f-6873e86f958b/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A ZJU100 professor at college of computer science and technology, Zhejiang University, China. He received his Ph.D. from the Penn State University, USA, in 2014. His research interests cover hardware-software integrated data verification, intelligent connected vehicle security, and AI-enhanced autonomous driving test. He has published research papers in premium venues, including TCHES, TCAD, TC, HOST. He has collaborated with multiple leading vehicle enterprises and research institutions, including Huawei, Zeekr, Geely, etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haoting Shen&#39;s Session</title>
      <link>/sessions/haoting-shens-session-896382/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sessions/haoting-shens-session-896382/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Usually, you would find a session description here. But, this is not a real session submission, so let just say we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about Technology, Interview, Consumer. Ha!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kun Yang</title>
      <link>/speakers/kun-yang-2b786b92-ff85-4834-a3ea-995c81716f3c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/speakers/kun-yang-2b786b92-ff85-4834-a3ea-995c81716f3c/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A ZJU100 professor at college of computer science and technology, Zhejiang University, China. He received his Ph.D. from the University of Florida, USA, in 2018. He previously served as a Senior Security Architect at NVIDIA Corporation. His research focuses on secure chip architectures, hardware-software integrated security architectures, and intelligent connected vehicle security. He has published numerous research papers in leading journals and conferences, such as TCAD, TC, DAC, ICCAD, HOST, BlackHat USA, etc. He was honored with the sole first-place Best Paper Award at the 2020 NVIDIA NTECH Conference, and received a Best Paper Award Nomination at the 2016 IEEE HOST. He has collaborated with multiple leading enterprises and research institutions, including Huawei, Ant Group, Horizon Robotics, H3C, Zeekr, Geely, etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kun Yang&#39;s Session</title>
      <link>/sessions/kun-yangs-session-896375/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sessions/kun-yangs-session-896375/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Usually, you would find a session description here. But, this is not a real session submission, so let just say we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about Technology, Interview, Consumer. Ha!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/location/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors &amp; Partners</title>
      <link>/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sponsors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xiaohang Wang</title>
      <link>/speakers/xiaohang-wang-90831a01-8501-4464-a604-af4c65c119a5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/speakers/xiaohang-wang-90831a01-8501-4464-a604-af4c65c119a5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Received the B. Eng. and Ph. D. degree in communication and electronic engineering from Zhejiang University, in 2006 and 2011, respectively. He is currently a professor at Zhejiang University. He was the receipt of PDP 2015 and VLSI-SoC 2014 Best Paper Awards. His research interests include vehicle security and many-core systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Organizing experience:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Session organizer, CODES+ISSS 2025&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Session organizer NoCS 2018&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Selected Publications:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Xiaohang Wang, Yifan Wang, Yingtao Jiang, Amit Kumar Singh, Mei Yang, On Task Mapping in Multi-chiplet Based Many-Core Systems to Optimize Inter- and Intra-chiplet Communications. TC 2025&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Shengjie Wang, Xiaohang Wang, Yingtao Jiang, Amit Kumar Singh, Mei Yang, Letian Huang, Modeling and Analysis of Thermal Covert Channel Attacks in Many-core Systems. TC 2023&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Shengyan Wen, Xiaohang Wang, Amit Kumar Singh, Yingtao Jiang, Mei Yang, Performance Optimization of Many-Core Systems by Exploiting Task Migration and Dark Core Allocation. TC 2022&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xiaohang Wang&#39;s Session</title>
      <link>/sessions/xiaohang-wangs-session-896384/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sessions/xiaohang-wangs-session-896384/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Usually, you would find a session description here. But, this is not a real session submission, so let just say we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about Technology, Interview, Consumer. Ha!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang Yin</title>
      <link>/speakers/yang-yin-7cc3eadc-78a4-4585-9830-9ced29df41cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/speakers/yang-yin-7cc3eadc-78a4-4585-9830-9ced29df41cd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The cybersecurity technical director of the Geely R&amp;amp;D Center, the cybersecurity technical leader in global Geely Group, also the department manager of the cybersecurity department, serving as an adjunct professor in Zhejiang University and Ningbo University, technical expert of Working Party on Automated/Autonomous and Connected Vehicles (GRVA) under UNECE World Forum for Harmonization of Vehicle Regulations (WP.29), technical expert in China National Technical Committee of Auto Standardization, and China Communications Standards Association. His work focuses on the cybersecurity implementation in connected vehicles, including cybersecurity design, pen testing, data protection and AI security and safety in autonomous vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang Yin&#39;s Session</title>
      <link>/sessions/yang-yins-session-896389/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sessions/yang-yins-session-896389/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Usually, you would find a session description here. But, this is not a real session submission, so let just say we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about Technology, Interview, Consumer. Ha!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
