<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshop on </title>
    <link>/categories/workshop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshop on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/categories/workshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cutting-Edge Research and Technological Breakthroughs</title>
      <link>/sessions/cutting-edge-research-and-technological-breakthroughs-896375/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sessions/cutting-edge-research-and-technological-breakthroughs-896375/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From a research perspective, this session will explore several critical technological domains: 1) vehicle security chips: design of high-reliability, low-power hardware trust roots and automotive-grade certification mechanisms. 2) Data-bus intrusion detection: real-time detection of multimodal sensor data and anomaly detection techniques. 3) Human-vehicle interaction privacy: privacy leakage prevention for biometric and voice-controlled interaction hardware. 4) Environmental perception reliability: anti-physical interference and data integrity verification for LiDAR, cameras, and other perception hardware.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industry Practices and Security Frameworks</title>
      <link>/sessions/industry-practices-and-security-frameworks-896389/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sessions/industry-practices-and-security-frameworks-896389/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Centered on practical demands from intelligent vehicle manufacturers, this session will systematically examine mainstream vehicle information security frameworks (e.g., distributed security architectures, centralized protection platforms) and analyze their limitations in hardware-layer implementations. Discussions will emphasize standardization strategies to enhance intrinsic security capabilities of in-vehicle hardware systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
