<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lightning Talk on </title>
    <link>/categories/lightning-talk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lightning Talk on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/categories/lightning-talk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Noah&#39;s Session</title>
      <link>/sessions/noahs-session-729578/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sessions/noahs-session-729578/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Usually, you would find a session description here. But, this is not a real session submission, so let just say we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about Coffee, Human resources, Illustration. Ha!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The History of Another Family</title>
      <link>/sessions/the-history-of-another-family-844991/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sessions/the-history-of-another-family-844991/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The surname &amp;ldquo;Smith&amp;rdquo; is one of the most common surnames in the English-speaking world. It originates from the Old English word &amp;ldquo;smitan,&amp;rdquo; which means &amp;ldquo;to smite&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;to strike.&amp;rdquo; This name was typically given to blacksmiths, who were essential members of medieval communities due to their skills in metalworking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Smith family name has been recorded in England since the Anglo-Saxon period, and it spread to other parts of the British Isles and beyond with the expansion of the British Empire. Many Smiths emigrated to the United States, Canada, Australia, and other countries, where the name remains prevalent.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The History of the Doe Family</title>
      <link>/sessions/the-history-of-the-doe-family-844985/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/sessions/the-history-of-the-doe-family-844985/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Doe family has a rich and varied history. The surname “Doe” is believed to have Norman origins, arriving in England after the Norman Conquest of 1066. The family originally lived in Somerset, and their name is thought to derive from the Norman French “Castle of O” or “D’O,” meaning &amp;ldquo;from O&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Doe family held lands in Lancashire from very early times, granted by Duke William of Normandy for their assistance at the Battle of Hastings in 10661. Over the centuries, the surname has seen various spellings, including Doe and Dow, due to the lack of standardized spelling in Old and Middle English.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
